autoanything.com 2011-12-30

# AutoAnything Privacy Policy

Take a moment to check out AutoAnything's policies and related information

  * AutoAnything's Lower Price Guarantee
  * Save up to 40%
  * Privacy policy
  * Safe & secure shopping
  * Affiliate program
  * Problems receiving AutoAnything e-mail
  * Legal notice, terms & conditions
  * CARB Exempt Information
  * Contact information

## AutoAnything's Lower Price Guarantee

**You will never pay more for any product at AutoAnything–guaranteed!**

If you happen to find the same product at a lower price, we will refund the difference - plus $1.00 - promptly.

And, to show our commitment to you, you have 1 FULL Year of price protection from the date of your purchase.

### Price match for products you would like to purchase

If you would like to purchase a product from AutoAnything and you see it advertised at a lower price somewhere else, contact our Auto Accessory Specialists toll-free at (800) 874-8888. We will review your request and place your order for the lower price.

Please note: Processing your order at the lower match price is done at the discretion of AutoAnything and is subject to evaluation using the terms and conditions below.

Processing your order at the lower match price is done at the discretion of AutoAnything and is subject to evaluation using the terms and conditions below.

### Price match for products you have already purchased

Email us at [customerservice@autoanything.com](mailto:customerservice@autoanything.com), providing the lower price, where you found it and the date you purchased the item from us. We will look into your order and process your refund. You will receive confirmation of the refund by email within 1-2 business days.

Processing your order at the lower match price is done at the discretion of AutoAnything and is subject to evaluation using the terms and conditions below.

### Terms and conditions

Price comparison includes merchandise selling price plus equivalent shipping method, handling charges, and sales tax. The item also needs to be the identical product and in new and unused condition. The item needs to be in stock and available for purchase from an authorized dealer and not a pricing error. Excludes rebates, liquidations, auction sites such as Ebay, and employee discounts. Price match discounts cannot be combined with AutoAnything promotional offers.

Expedited shipping offers and orders shipped outside of the Unites States or Territories may not be eligible for price matching. AutoAnything reserves the right to limit the amount of price match requests per customer.

On rare occasions, erroneous price or availability listings may appear on this site or independently operated affiliate sites. While we apologize for the inconvenience such an error may cause, AutoAnything reserves the right to correct inaccuracies at any time, with or without notice, and update any related orders. We also reserve the right not to price match against any erroneous price listing on this site or any other site. For more information on site errors and corrections, please see our full terms and conditions.

* * *

## Save up to 40%

At AutoAnything you can save up to 40% off list price every day. More often than not, "List Price" is the suggested retail price of a product as set by the manufacturer or supplier. In the very few cases where the manufacturer or supplier has not provided a suggested retail price, the "List Price" represents either 1 - the manufacturer's suggested retail price for a comparable product; 2 - an approximate price formulated using standard wholesale/retail markups for this particular type of product; 3 - the "Comparison Price" for the same or comparable product as advertised by at least one other vendor.

The "List Price" is not necessarily the lowest price and often can be higher than the actual price at which the product is commonly being sold or offered. "You Save" on our site is arrived at by deducting our price from "List Price" and in some cases may not equate to your actual savings since retail prices available to you may vary. 

Please keep in mind, however, the assurance of AutoAnything's 1-Year Low Price Guarantee - find it anywhere else for less and we'll beat that price, for up to one year from the date of your purchase.

## Privacy Policy

### Information Gathered By AutoAnything.com

This is AutoAnything.com's ("AutoAnything.com") online privacy policy ("Policy"). This policy applies only to activities AutoAnything.com engages in on its website and does not apply to AutoAnything.com activities that are "offline" or unrelated to the website. AutoAnything.com collects certain anonymous data regarding the usage of the website. This information does not personally identify users, by itself or in combination with other information, and is gathered to improve the performance of the website. The anonymous data collected by the AutoAnything.com website can include information such as the type of browser you are using, browsing patterns, originating web pages, number of visits to AutoAnything.com, vehicle selections, items viewed, pages viewed, and the length of the visit to the website.

You may also be asked to provide personally identifiable information on the AutoAnything.com website, which may include your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address. In addition, if a purchase is made, we collect credit card information, billing and shipping address, other customer information, vehicle information, information regarding prior purchases, and information concerning the dollar amount of the purchase, the date of the purchase, and the specific items purchased. This information is collectively referred to as "personally identifiable information." This information can be gathered when feedback or e-mails are sent to AutoAnything.com, when you register for services, when you voluntarily post information in chat rooms, blogs, message boards or other public forums on AutoAnything.com, when you make purchases via the website, or when you enter information in the checkout process but do not complete your checkout. In all such cases you have the option of providing us with personally identifiable information. You may always choose not to provide us with your personally identifiable information, but you then may not be able to participate in the particular activity that requires such information. If you do provide us with your personally identifiable information, you agree that we may contact you to provide you with information we believe may be of interest to you.

### Email Opt-Out

You always have the option to opt-out of our non-transactional emails via a link in the footer of all non-transactional email messages. Alternatively, you may email autoanything@email.autoanything.com at anytime and ask to be removed.

Some communications (e.g. important account notifications and billing information) are considered transactional and are necessary for all AutoAnything customers. If you have any issues with transactional emails, please email us at [customerservice@autoanything.com](mailto:customerservice@autoanything.com)

### Cookies: Web Beacons

We use cookies to track certain browsing patterns on the website. Cookies are small bits of data cached in a user's browser. AutoAnything.com utilizes cookies to personalize your experience on AutoAnything.com, assist you in using AutoAnything.com, and allow us to compile site usage statistics to better improve our goods, services and products. Cookies may also be used to conduct marketing and promotional efforts, tailor advertisements to your browser, or determine the popularity of our content. The cookies collect certain identifying information, including customer identifiers generated by us, as well as a visitor ID that will, in certain circumstances, be matched with personally identifiable information. However, no other user information is gathered by cookies. AutoAnything.com pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons or action tags that allow AutoAnything.com to count users who have visited those pages and deliver co-branded services. Web beacons are invisible to you. Unlike cookies, Web beacons are not placed on your computer. Web beacons collect only anonymous online behavioral data and/or anonymous identifiers, such as an anonymous cookie ID number. AutoAnything.com pages may also contain Web beacons placed by third parties in order to compile aggregated statistics and help determine the effectiveness of joint promotional or advertising efforts.

### Use and Disclosure Information

Except as otherwise stated below, we do not sell, trade or rent your personally identifiable information collected on the site to others. The information collected by our site is used to confirm and process orders, to keep you informed about your order status, to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you, to obtain reviews, ratings or testimonials relating to your experience with AutoAnything products purchased, and for statistical purposes for improving our site. We will disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties for tracking purposes, to charge your credit card (or process your check or money order, as appropriate), fill your order, improve the functionality of our site, perform statistical and data analyses, deliver your order and deliver promotional emails to you from us. For example, we must release your credit card number to confirm payment; and release your mailing address information to the delivery service to deliver products that you ordered.

AutoAnything.com may use non-personal "aggregated data" to enhance the operation of our website, or analyze interest in the areas of our website. Moreover, we may in some circumstances disclose personally identifiable information to third parties to enhance your experience on our website. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

Additionally, if you provide AutoAnything.com with content for publishing or feedback (such as information you elect to post in chat rooms, blogs, message boards or other public forums on AutoAnything.com), we may publish your user name or other identifying data along with such content. If you choose to voluntarily post information in chat rooms, blogs, message boards or other public forums on AutoAnything.com, that information can be accessed by AutoAnything.com and by the public, and can in turn be used by AutoAnything.com or by the public for any purpose, including, without limitation, sending you unsolicited communications. We are not responsible for the information you choose to submit in these public forums. If AutoAnything.com determines, in its sole discretion, that any information you have posted in these public forums is objectionable, AutoAnything.com shall have the right to remove such information from AutoAnything.com and to prevent you from posting additional information.

AutoAnything.com may also disclose personally identifiable information in order to respond to a subpoena, court order or other such request. AutoAnything.com may also provide such personally identifiable information to state and federal governmental agencies as required by applicable laws and regulations, and as required to comply with subpoenas or other legal process. Your personally identifiable information may be provided to a party if AutoAnything.com files for bankruptcy, or there is a transfer of the assets or ownership of AutoAnything.com in connection with proposed or consummated corporate reorganizations, such as mergers or acquisitions.

From time to time we may disclose personally identifiable information to direct marketing companies for trade or rental purposes. You may opt out, or instruct us not to distribute such information to third parties in the future by sending an email with such instructions to [info@autoanything.com](mailto:info@autoanything.com); however, we may not be able to provide you our full range of services if we cannot distribute certain Personally Identifiable Information.

If you choose to participate in activities offered through co-branded sites, you will have the opportunity to affirmatively consent to the transfer of certain personally identifiable information to the co-branded sites, as appropriate, such as your name, date of birth, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, expiration date and other information necessary for your participation in the co-branded sites.

### Other Websites

AutoAnything.com is not responsible for the privacy policies of websites to which it links, including co-branded sites. If you provide any information to such third parties, different rules regarding the collection and use of your personal information may apply. We strongly suggest you review such third party's privacy policies before consenting to the transfer of data or providing any data to them. We are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties. Please be aware that our sites may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of those Web sites linked to our site is not covered by this Policy. These other sites may send their own cookies or clear GIFs to users, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact these entities directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect.

### Security

AutoAnything.com takes appropriate steps to ensure data privacy and security including through various hardware and software methodologies. Your transaction is secure in that you would pay nothing in the event that an unauthorized charge was made to your credit card after purchasing from AutoAnything. However, AutoAnything.com cannot guarantee the security of any information that is disclosed online.

### Affiliate Program

AutoAnything has Affiliate Programs which are operated by Performics and Commission Junction who may gather information from you. Such information is not governed by the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### Sweepstakes, Competitions and Contestants

If you enter any of the above you may be asked to provide contact information which may be used for administration and promotional purposes. Your consent to such use is a condition of your participation. The awarding of any prize to you will be subject to the execution of liability, Publicity Releases and an Affidavit of Eligibility in compliance with the rules applicable to the relevant promotional activity.

### Collecting Information on Children

AutoAnything.com does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Children are not permitted to use the AutoAnything.com website or services, and AutoAnything.com requests that children under the age of 13 not submit any personal information to the website. Since information regarding children under the age of 13 is not collected, AutoAnything.com does not knowingly distribute personal information regarding children under the age of 13.

### Corrections and Updates

If you wish to modify or update any information AutoAnything.com has received, please contact [customerservice@autoanything.com.](mailto:customerservice@autoanything.com)

### Modifications of the Privacy Policy

AutoAnything.com reserves the rights to modify its privacy policy at any time and will notify you by posting an amendment to the privacy policy on the website. Such modifications will become effective on the day they are posted. AutoAnything.com encourages you to frequently review the privacy policy for any modifications.

* * *

## Safe & Secure Shopping

The AutoAnything Security Guarantee protects you while you shop at AutoAnything so that you never have to worry about credit card safety. We guarantee that every transaction you make at AutoAnything will be safe. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your credit card as a result of shopping at AutoAnything. We have processed more than 500,000 problem free orders. AutoAnything servers use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an encryption technology that works with Netscape, Microsoft Internet Explorer, AOL, and Apple's Safari's browser. This ensures that only AutoAnything can read your personal information. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. We will, however, transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

After you click on the "checkout" button, be sure that the website's URL always begins with https://www.autoanything.com/

The "s" in "https://" at the beginning of the URL means you are logging into a secure page. If the URL does not begin with https, you are not on an AutoAnything page.

AutoAnything has also obtained a digital certificate from Network Solutions, a leading provider of Internet trust services. When you enter a secured portion of our site, an image of a closed lock or a solid key should appear in the bottom bar of your browser window. If you click on this image, a small popup window displaying site-security information will appear. This certificate guarantees that your personal information is being transmitted in secure (encrypted) form to an AutoAnything Web server, not to an unknown or unauthorized server.

Ultimately, your personal information is protected by the password you created when you registered for an account at AutoAnything on the "Log-In / Quick Checkout" page. Please keep this password confidential. No representative of AutoAnything will ever ask you for your password. The confidentiality of your password is yours to protect.

* * *

## Affiliate Program

AutoAnything's Top Affiliate Partners Earn Over $4,000 a month! Join our Affiliate Program and this could be you!

### Why should I become an AutoAnything affiliate?

  * AutoAnything's top partners earn over $4,000/month!
  * AutoAnything offers one of the highest commissions in our industry - receive a generous 8% commission!
  * Our average order level is high, meaning a high average commission payout per order for you.
  * AutoAnything provides you with opportunities to earn more cash with our monthly incentive programs! Contact me for information: [affiliatemarketing@autoanything.com](mailto:affiliatemarketing@autoanything.com)
  * Personal Attention - As your Affiliate Marketing Manager, I'm here full-time, dedicated to make your partnership a success! This means the most possible cash to you!
  * Partner with a trusted online leader.
  * It's easy and it's free!

### How does it work?

  * Click on one of the links below to join our program through [Google Affiliate Network](https://www.connectcommerce.com/secure/partner_app.html?ccmid=K30464) or [Commission Junction](https://signup.cj.com/member/brandedPublisherSignUp.do?air_refmerchantid=1376813).
  * Read our affiliate agreement. 
  * Complete the online application. 
  * Once your application is approved (typically within 48 hours), you will receive an email notification with your login and linking instructions. 
  * Choose from a large, HOT inventory of text links, product links, data feeds, and banners to add to your site. Don't see a size you want? Email ME! [affiliatemarketing@autoanything.com](mailto:affiliatemarketing@autoanything.com)

That's all you have to do to start your prosperous affiliate partnership with AutoAnything!

### Choose either below to sign up (or click for more information):

[](https://www.connectcommerce.com/secure/partner_app.html?ccmid=K30464) or [](https://signup.cj.com/member/brandedPublisherSignUp.do?air_refmerchantid=1376813)

### What if I need help?

Please don't hesitate to contact me with any questions, comments, or requests.

Thank You,  
Affiliate Marketing Manager  
AutoAnything  

* * *

## Problems Receiving AutoAnything E-mail

If you have emailed any of our departments, but have not received a response, it may be that our email replies are being blocked by your browser settings, spam filters or by your internet service provider (ISP).

Even legitimate commercial email, like email from our customer service departments or Order Status notifications can be blocked. If you believe this is happening, you may be able to add us to your Safe Sender List or address book to eliminate the problem. You may also want to review the help section of your email program or contact your ISP and see how to loosen the settings that filter or block email that you receive.

Once you've made changes to your settings, email us once more and we'll gladly answer your question again. If you still do not receive a reply, email us with "Contact Requested" in the subject line with your telephone number in the body of the email and one of our friendly customer service representatives will promptly contact you.

* * *

## Legal Notice, Terms & Conditions

Blue Ribbon Motoring LLC d/b/a AutoAnything ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. Please refer to the legal notice below for terms of use. This Web site is operated by AutoAnything. The Web site address for AutoAnything is [http://www.AutoAnything.com](http://www.autoanything.com/). The mailing address for Blue Ribbon Motoring, LLC is 6602 Convoy Ct, Suite 200, San Diego, California 92123.

All users of this Web site agree that their access to and use of this Web site are subject to the terms and conditions set forth in this legal notice and all applicable laws, and that any such access or use is undertaken at the user's own risk. These terms and conditions further are subject to change at any time without prior notice. Any such changes will be reflected on the Legal Notice page of the AutoAnything Web site.

All content, graphics, code and software used on or incorporated into this Web site, and the arrangement or integration of all such content, graphics, code and software, are subject to any copyrights held by or licensed to Blue Ribbon Motoring LLC and/or AutoAnything or in respect of which Blue Ribbon Motoring LLC and/or AutoAnything is protected or entitled to by operation of any law, and all rights thereto are specifically reserved. Permission is granted to electronically copy and print hard copies of pages from this Web site solely for personal, non-commercial purposes related to the placement of an order or shopping at AutoAnything. Any other use of this Web site content, or information contained in this Web site is strictly prohibited, unless the written permission of AutoAnything first is obtained.

This Web site may contain typographical errors or inaccuracies and may not be complete or current. AutoAnything therefore reserves the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions (including after an order has been submitted) and to change or update information at any time without prior notice. Please note that such errors, inaccuracies or omissions may relate to pricing and availability, and we reserve the right to cancel or refuse to accept any order placed based on incorrect pricing or availability information. We apologize for any inconvenience.

This Web site, and any information or content on this Web site, are provided "as is," with all faults. AutoAnything makes no representations or warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, with respect to this Web site or content or information available on or through this Web site. Except as otherwise provided under applicable laws, neither Blue Ribbon Motoring LLC nor its corporate affiliates, nor the directors, officers, employees, agents, contractors, successors or assigns of each, shall be liable for any damages whatsoever arising out of or related to the use of this Web site or any other Web site linked to this Web site. This limitation of liability applies to direct, indirect, consequential, special, punitive or other damages you or others may suffer, as well as damages for lost profits, business interruption or the loss of data or information, even if Blue Ribbon Motoring LLC and/or AutoAnything is notified in advance of the potential for any such damages. "AutoAnything," as well as page headers, custom graphics, buttons, images and other content on this Web site are subject to trademark, service mark, trade dress, copyright and or other proprietary or intellectual property rights or licenses held by Blue Ribbon Motoring LLC and/or AutoAnything or in respect of which Blue Ribbon Motoring LLC and/or AutoAnything is protected or entitled to by operation of any law. Other trademarks, product names and company names or logos used on this Web site are the property of their respective owners. Except as expressly authorized, the use or misuse of any trademarks, trade names, logos, images, graphics or content from this Web site is strictly prohibited.

Blue Ribbon Motoring LLC and/or AutoAnything does not make any representations or warranties about any Web site you may access through this Web site. Any such Web site is independent from Blue Ribbon Motoring LLC and/or AutoAnything, and AutoAnything has no control over, or responsibility with respect to, the information provided or activities undertaken by any such Web site. A link between AutoAnything and another Web site further does not mean that AutoAnything endorses that Web site. AutoAnything does not want to receive confidential, proprietary or trade secret information through this Web site (excluding information related to any order you submit). Please note that any information, materials, suggestions, ideas or comments sent to AutoAnything will be deemed non-confidential. By submitting any such information, you are granting Blue Ribbon Motoring LLC and/or AutoAnything an irrevocable and unrestricted license to use, modify, reproduce, transmit, display and distribute such materials, information, suggestions, ideas or comments for any purpose whatsoever. However, we will not use your name in connection with any such materials, information, suggestions, ideas or comments unless we first obtain your permission or otherwise are required by law to do so.

* * *

## CARB Exempt Information

Parts and accessories which are not “CARB exempt” may violate emission control system anti-tampering laws, and may not be legal for highway use in your state.

CARB (California Air Resources Board) sets motor vehicle emissions standards for the state of California; however, the following states also adhere to the CARB standard.

  * Arizona
  * California
  * Connecticut
  * District of Columbia
  * Maine
  * Maryland
  * Massachusetts
  * New Jersey
  * New Mexico
  * New York
  * Oregon
  * Pennsylvania
  * Rhode Island
  * Vermont
  * Washington

Please check your state and local laws for details.

* * *

## Contact Information

We're always here to help! Whether you contact us by phone or email, we'll give a prompt reply to your questions, comments or concerns.

For assistance from one of our knowledgeable Auto Accessory Specialists, call toll-free at 1-800-874-8888. They're happy to help!

### Mailing address/company offices

AutoAnything  
6602 Convoy Ct, Suite 200  
San Diego, CA 92111

### Telephone

**Customer service:**|  1-800-874-8888  
---|---  
**Phone sales:**|  1-800-874-8888  
**Direct:**|  858-569-8111  
**Fax:**|  858-569-8503  

### Hours

**Phone Sales (All times PST)**

Monday - Thursday - 5:30am - 8:00pm

Friday - 5:30am - 5:00pm

Saturday - 6:00am - 5:00pm

Sunday - 6:00am - 5:00pm

 **Customer Service**

Monday - Friday 6:00am - 5:00pm

### Email

**Order by email:**| [sales@autoanything.com](mailto:sales@autoanything.com)  
---|---  
**Express shipping:**| [expressshipping@autoanything.com](mailto:expressshipping@autoanything.com)  
**Canada Orders:**| [canadashipping@autoanything.com](mailto:canadashipping@autoanything.com)  
**Order status info:**| [orderstatus@autoanything.com](mailto:orderstatus@autoanything.com)  
**Cancel an order:**| [cancel@autoanything.com](mailto:cancel@autoanything.com)  
**Returns & exchanges:**| [returns@autoanything.com](mailto:returns@autoanything.com)  
**Job opportunities:**| [careers@autoanything.com](mailto:careers@autoanything.com)  
**Affiliate program:**| [affiliatemarketing@autoanything.com](mailto:affiliatemarketing@autoanything.com)  
**Customer Service:**| [customerservice@autoanything.com](mailto:customerservice@autoanything.com)
